<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>FIX API Related Posts on FIX API PRO</title>
    <link>https://www.fixpro.cc/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in FIX API Related Posts on FIX API PRO</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.fixpro.cc/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Exante Crypto and FIX API</title>
      <link>https://www.fixpro.cc/exante-crypto-fix-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.fixpro.cc/exante-crypto-fix-api/</guid>
      <description>Exante Crypto and FIX API Exante Crypto, a cryptocurrency exchange and leading fintech company, today announced its arm of institutional services for digital assets. Exante Crypto&amp;lsquo;s launch of FIX API, further accelerates the adoption from its growing list of institutional customers, who want to add Bitcoin and other cryptocurrency trading strategies to their offerings.
Exante Crypto&amp;lsquo;s FIX API trading, is available to institutional investors, brokers, private traders, hedge funds, asset managers, corporations, VCs, high net worth individuals, endowments, family offices and private wealth managers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ATC Brokers and FIX API</title>
      <link>https://www.fixpro.cc/atc-brokers-fix-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.fixpro.cc/atc-brokers-fix-api/</guid>
      <description>ATC Brokers and FIX API ATC brokers Ltd, the institutional arm of ATC, focusing on FIX API, Hedge Funds, Family Offices, B2B, Asset Managers&amp;rsquo;s, and spread betting accounts, has reported positive trend growth for its trading volumes for the year of 2020 and 2021.
ATC brokers Ltd announces year on year total volumes between 2020 and 2021, have grown compared to earlier last year when the coronavirus pandemic created unprecedented volatility across varying asset classes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exchanges Launch FIX API</title>
      <link>https://www.fixpro.cc/exchanges-launch-fix-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.fixpro.cc/exchanges-launch-fix-api/</guid>
      <description>Exchanges Launch FIX API Several exchanges with FIX API, the multi-asset class trading platforms, announced recently that they launched and traded the anonymous interbank FX Swaps order book with streaming quotes.
The trade, conducted with the exchanges&amp;rsquo; central counterparty partner Standard Chartered Bank, represents a landmark in this $3.2 T/day* market.
In addition to the central counterparty option, bilateral trading for short tenors is also available. Trading in the one-week tenor – the most liquid part of the market which accounts for around 65% of transacted volume – is free on the Exchanges&amp;rsquo; platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Order Management System and FIX API</title>
      <link>https://www.fixpro.cc/new-order-management-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.fixpro.cc/new-order-management-system/</guid>
      <description>New Order Management System and FIX API Fintechee, a leader in technology solutions for the automated trading, FIX API, white label broker Forex and expert advisor studio, will launch a sell-side Order Management System making clients to streamline their trading operations later 2021.
Fintechee FIX API trading Platform is a leading provider of professional trading technology solutions for Forex, Cryptocurrency and CFD markets. With over clients including leading brokers, clearing firms and prop groups in over countries, Fintechee provides solutions tailored to clients’ needs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>